I was gonna go for a walk out 4:76 which
is ironic because this is what I'm gonna
be talking about it is pokemons go came
out I don't even know I say it was a
year ago because you're still closing so
a year ago pokemon gold came out and
people were obsessed with it for a
period of time you know there's still
people who play it and I think a lot of
us had that similar idea of like wow how
do we harness this getting people out of
their houses actually walking around
meeting other people using geocaching I
don't have an idea related to that
itself but what a great idea we need to
figure out something to do with that
it's not branded Pokemon that's or it is
but more of them so we can all have them
and I'll have ways to connect and yeah I
gamify it I think that it would be so
much fun so a Pokemon go for Humanity is
Apple number 76 now I'm gonna go for an
actual law